♪♪♪
♪ WE COULDN'T TURN AROUND ♪
♪ TIL WE WERE UPSIDE DOWN ♪
♪ I'LL BE THE BAD GUY NOW ♪
♪ BUT KNOW I AIN'T TOO PROUD ♪
♪ I COULDN'T BE THERE ♪
♪ EVEN WHEN I TRIED ♪
♪ YOU DON'T BELIEVE IT ♪
♪ WE DO THIS EVERY TIME ♪
♪ SEASONS CHANGE ♪
♪ AND OUR LOVE WENT COLD ♪
♪ FEED THE FLAME ♪
♪ BECAUSE WE CAN'T LET GO ♪
♪ RUNAWAY ♪
♪ BUT WE'RE RUNNING IN CIRCLES ♪
♪ RUNAWAY, RUNAWAY ♪
♪ I DARE YOU TO DO SOMETHING ♪
♪ I'M WAITING ON YOU AGAIN ♪
♪ SO I DON'T TAKE THE BLAME ♪
♪ RUNAWAY ♪
♪ BUT WE'RE RUNNING IN CIRCLES ♪
♪ RUNAWAY, RUNAWAY, RUNAWAY ♪
♪ LET GO ♪
♪ I GOT A FEELING ♪
♪ THAT IT'S TIME TO LET GO ♪
♪ I SAID SO ♪
♪ I KNEW THAT THIS WAS DOOMED ♪
♪ FROM THE GET GO ♪
♪ YOU THOUGHT
THAT IT WAS SPECIAL ♪
♪ SPECIAL ♪
♪ BUT IT WAS JUST
THE SEX THOUGH ♪
♪ THE SEX THOUGH ♪
♪ AND I STILL HEAR THE ECHOES ♪
♪ THE ECHOES ♪
♪ I GOT A FEELING THAT IT'S TIME
TO LET IT GO ♪
♪ LET IT GO ♪
♪ SEASONS CHANGE ♪
♪ AND OUR LOVE WENT COLD ♪
♪ FEED THE FLAME ♪
♪ BECAUSE WE CAN'T LET GO ♪
♪ RUNAWAY ♪
♪ BUT WE'RE RUNNING IN CIRCLES ♪
♪ RUNAWAY, RUNAWAY ♪
♪ I DARE YOU TO DO SOMETHING ♪
♪ I'M WAITING ON YOU AGAIN ♪
♪ SO I DON'T TAKE THE BLAME ♪
♪ RUNAWAY BUT WE'RE RUNNING IN
CIRCLES ♪
♪ RUNAWAY, RUNAWAY, RUNAWAY ♪
♪ MAYBE YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND ♪
♪ WHAT I'M GOING THRU ♪
♪ IT'S ONLY ME ♪
♪ WHAT YOU GOT TO LOSE ♪
♪ MAKE UP YOUR MIND ♪
♪ TELL ME WHAT ARE
YOU GONNA DO ♪
♪ IT'S ONLY ME ♪
♪ LET IT GO ♪
♪ SEASONS CHANGE ♪
♪ AND OUR LOVE WENT COLD ♪
♪ FEED THE FLAME ♪
♪ BECAUSE WE CAN'T LET GO ♪
♪ RUNAWAY ♪
♪ BUT WE'RE RUNNING IN CIRCLES ♪
♪ RUNAWAY, RUNAWAY ♪
♪ I DARE YOU TO DO SOMETHING ♪
♪ I'M WAITING ON YOU AGAIN ♪
♪ SO I DON'T TAKE THE BLAME ♪
♪ RUNAWAY BUT WE'RE
RUNNING IN CIRCLES ♪
♪ RUNAWAY, RUNAWAY ♪
♪ RUNAWAY ♪